<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VRcollab</title>
    <link>https://vrcollab.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on VRcollab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:16:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vrcollab.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BIM Integrations, Colour Markups &amp; VDC Coordination — VRcollab v0.9.10</title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/posts/v0.9.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/posts/v0.9.10/</guid>
      <description>New BIM &amp;amp; Format Import Integrations Added: Revit 2019 , Navisworks 18, Archicad 22 (Beta), Direct OBJ Import
Supported as of v0.9.10: Revit(2014–2019), Sketchup(2016–2018), Archicad(21–22), Rhino3D 6, Navisworks 18, OBJ
Formats Merge Feature: For eg. Archicad and Revit Models merged in VRcollab, with ability to access full data from both softwares for purposes of BIM VR coordination.
3D scan  Point Cloud Data  OBJ  VRcollab Import Direct OBJ imports allow for 3D scanned terrain or building to be imported into VRcollab for merging with any of the above integrated formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect to your Stakeholders in 3 Easy Steps! Plus Mini-maps, Gridlines and more - VRcollab LITE v0.10.0</title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/posts/v0.10.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/posts/v0.10.0/</guid>
      <description>In version v0.10.0, we have completely reiterated the design of the launcher, with a more focused workflow centred around stakeholder collaboration and data communication.
Does your VRcollab Launcher look different? Don&amp;rsquo;t fret!
Also introducing multi-language support, starting with our Mandarin Language support, with many other languages coming in the next few months.
Multiuser Internet Coordination One key feature we are proud of is the ease at which the new launcher enables users to host or join coordination meetings with stakeholders from around the world in a couple of easy steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Office Setups for Virtual Design Construction (VDC) Coordination</title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/posts/office-vdc-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/posts/office-vdc-setup/</guid>
      <description>With the growing adoption of BIM (Building Information Modelling) in the last decade, construction methodologies have seen an evolution towards lean construction and integrated project delivery. This entails the need for collaborative software, digitalisation of information, along with new organisational space approaches that are in tune to the Virtual Design Construction (VDC) framework.
 #1: Co-located BIG Room As construction projects grow increasingly more complex, in both scale and technical specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRcollab STUDIO 2.0: Are CAVEs replacing coordination rooms in Architecture and Construction?</title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/posts/vrcollab-studio-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/posts/vrcollab-studio-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Building design coordination has traditionally been done in both meeting and board rooms, usually in front of a large screen while stakeholder’s perspective are dictated by a single pilot. Navigating BIM software to the best possible perspective in order to coordinate both clashes and design.
This tedious process is further complicated by another two professionals whose role is to capture the projected screen and annotate important considerations. All this is then finally consolidated for further interrogation and remodelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why include VR In BIM execution plan</title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/posts/why-include-vr-in-bim-execution-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/posts/why-include-vr-in-bim-execution-plan/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Architecture, Engineering &amp;amp; Construction projects have long been hamstrung by delays and escalating costs due to a myriad of unforeseen factors and events during the planning and execution of complex projects. While economic risks can never be entirely mitigated, the advent of new technology has always been a key driver for change.
Why is the AEC industry adopting Virtual Reality? Over the past two decades, progress within the AEC industry has largely been the result of a few technological shifts that have transformed the way in which buildings are fundamentally conceived, designed and built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} VRcollab is a Singaporean software start-up that is invested by SGinnovate, Entrepreneur First and HTC VIVE. First incorporated in December 2016, VRcollab’s mission is to redefine collaboration and design coordination in the Architecture, Engineering and Construction (AEC) Industry.
This is possible because of VRcollab’s Core Technology that automatically converts BIM (Building Information Models) for use in Virtual Reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/account/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/account/</guid>
      <description>Account Overview - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}   {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Verify your account email address before you use VRcollab.  License details Your license will expire on N.A..
Download VRcollab Lite Buy License  Account details  Email address  Resend verification email Logout   New Password Password must be at least 10 chars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/certified-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/certified-professionals/</guid>
      <description>Certified Professionals - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Certified Professionals   In recognition of the pursuit of excellence and knowledge in the field of Virtual Design Coordination.  The VRcollab Certified Professionals Program recognises individuals who have attended and trained in Virtual Building Information Model (BIM) Coordination using the VRcollab LITE Software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/confirm_email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/confirm_email/</guid>
      <description> About - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }}  Your email has been verified.
Go back to account details   Unknown error occurred.
Go back to account details     const oobCode = $.query(&#34;oobCode&#34;); $.account.verify_email(oobCode).then(_ = { $(&#34;#success&#34;).show(); $(&#34;#error&#34;).hide(); }).catch(_ = { });  {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }}  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/lite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/lite/</guid>
      <description> VRcollab Lite - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;lite/cover.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;lite/intergration.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;lite/benefit.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;lite/features.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;lite/testimonials.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;pricing.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;social.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }}   baguetteBox.run(&#39;.tz-gallery&#39;);   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/login/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/login/</guid>
      <description>Login - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Login   Email address  Password  Forget password?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Not have an account yet? Register.
Login      (() = { function setSuccessMessage(message) { if (!message) { $(&#34;#successMessage&#34;).hide(); } else { $(&#34;#successMessage&#34;).html(message); $(&#34;#successMessage&#34;).show(); } } function setErrorMessage(message) { if (!message) { $(&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/purchase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/purchase/</guid>
      <description>About - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Purchase Please provide us your details. Our sales person will contact you in 24 hours.
   -- Request for Quotation Product VRcollab Lite VRcollab Studio   Quantity Please let us know the quantity you are requesting.   Name Please provide us your name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/register/</guid>
      <description>Register - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Supports BIM Software: Revit, Sketchup, Archicad, Navisworks
VR Hardware: HTC VIVE, Occulus Rift, Windows MR Benefits and Features Depth &amp; Perspective Information, Faster Design Approvals, Intutitive Manipulation of BIM, Minimising Design Errors Measurements, BIM Object Data, Annotations, Daylight Analysis, Render Modes, Merge BIM Models, Multiuser Coordination, Desktop User Friendly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/reset_password/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/reset_password/</guid>
      <description>Login - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;hero.html&#34; . }} Reset Password   Password reset code  New Password Password must be at least 10 chars.   Confirm password Passwords must match.   Reset      (() = { function setSuccessMessage(message) { if (!message) { $(&#34;#successMessage&#34;).hide(); } else { $(&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vrcollab.com/studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vrcollab.com/studio/</guid>
      <description> VRcollab Studio - BIM and VDC Coordination in Virtual Reality {{ partial &#34;head.html&#34; . }}  {{ partial &#34;header.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;studio/cover.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;studio/features.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;studio/gallery.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;pricing.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;social.html&#34; . }} {{ partial &#34;footer.html&#34; . }}   baguetteBox.run(&#39;.tz-gallery&#39;);   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>